

# MD. RASHED MOSHARRAE

md.rasmos@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/mdrasmos



fb.com/md.rasmos



# **Professional Profile**

As a business graduate, I have more than 4 years of experience in several sectors. Customer relations, digital marketing, strategy, branding, advertising, technology and startups are few of those. Solving real life problem with creativity and efficiency intrigue me the most. Making a positive outcome through hard work, dedication and loyalty is what I strive for.

# **Experience**

**Beatnik** (November 2019-Current)

## Sr. Executive, Brand Communication

Communicating with clients like Marico Bangladesh and various third parties to formulate visual representation and briefs of projects. Acting as the primary point of contact for clients as well as the bridge between clients and the office( Designers, copywriters, planners, developers, community manager, production team and media team)

■ EndingScene Digital (January 2019-October 2019)

#### Digital Marketing Executive

Handling different clients like Guardian Life Insurance, Incepta Pharma, Regent Aviation Academy etc. to ensure smooth flow of digital campaigns on different medias. Keeping track of daily activities, deadline. Making monthly content & campaign plans in front of existing/potential new clients.

We Are X (May 2017-April 2018)

#### Project Team Leader

Responsibilities included overseeing recruitment and referring to project manager for final interview. Also training the team, creating roster and monitoring their performance and making reports about it on a daily basis. Creating content on a regular basis for social media team was also a major part of my job.

- □ Achievement: Best performing team for 2 consecutive months. Praised by the vice president of airtel Bangladesh.
- Offerali.com (January 2017-November 2017)
  Strategy Manager

As a strategy manager works varied into a wide range of tasks from making the 1st pitch doc to giving pitch in front of national and international investors, VC firms like 500 startups, Startup SG etc. in Singapore.

- □ Achievement: Group runner up in second round in Arena Pitch Battle 2017 Singapore. Won Tech Asia guiz contest, pitched in front of heavyweight investors and secured seed funding.
- Orangetoolz (August 2016-December 2016)

#### Content creator & Copywriter

Creating different interesting contents based on demand both in Bangla and mostly in English. Also made the potential design for new website and presented to different international client.

**Strategeek (**June 2016-May 2017)

#### Customer Engagement Officer

Worked for one of the biggest telco brands Robi Axiata, in their social media pages. Main job was handling queries in real time and making response content for the page.

□ Achievement: Won an office competition for promoting the brand most effectively.

#### **Education**

Bachelor of Business Administration, Marketing Institution: North South University Major in Marketing

■ Higher School Certificate, Business Studies Institution: Adamjee Cantonment College GPA 5.00 (2012)

■ Secondary School Certificate, Business Studies Institution: BAF Shaheen School GPA 4.81 (2010)

### Skills

Microsoft Office, Google Suit, Digital Marketing Strategy, Prof. Writing & Presentation, Digital Marketing Strategy, Adobe Creative Cloud, Fluent in Bengali & English, Prof. Writing & Presentation

#### **Interests**

Watching Sports, Movies, Space Exploration, Books, Listening to music, Writing, Playing guitar, Travelling.

# **Awards & Recognition**

Finalist: Robi R Venture 2.0 (2019)

One of the final top 7 Teams to get an investment offer from the investors out of 5000+ teams, from all over the Bangladesh.

Champion, Quiz Asia 2017, Singapore

Largest startup summit in Asia. Held at Singapore in 2017. Represented Bangladesh solely and fought for seed level funding. Won the quiz event and got opportunity to do an elevator pitch in front of heavy weight investors like facebook co-founder Eduardo Saverin. We were Offered a seed funding on spot.

#### Reference

■ Mohammad Obidur Rahman
Head of Business Intelligence
We are X

Mob:+8801770116699 Mail:obidurr@justanx.com

■ Md Affan kajmi
Chief Executive Officer
Offerali.com

Mob:+8801926662284 Mail:olmisbd@gmail.com Asif Iqbal

Senior Brand Manager
Marico Bangladesh
Mob:+8801713755094
Mail:asif.iqbal@marico.com

■ Rubayet Saleheen

Director, Marketing

Guardian Life Insurance Ltd.

Mob:+01847131181

Mail:rubayet.saleheen@glilbd.com